This is the solutions video for printing the results.
本视频将讲解结果输出部分的解决方案
First we need to define the print results function.
首先 定义函数 print_results
The docstring indicates we have five input parameters.
这里的文档字符串指出我们有五个输入参数
The last two have default arguments.
最后两个参数有默认值
Results_dic, the dictionary with the file name as its key,
第一个参数 results_dic 是一个字典 以文件名为键
and the list as its value.
以列表为值
This dictionary is needed to print the misclassified dogs and breeds.
我们需要借助该字典来输出分类错误的犬类和犬种
Results_stats, this dictionary is returned by the calculate_results_stats function.
第二个参数为 results_stats 该字典由函数 calculates_results_stats 返回而出
The dictionary contains all the percentage and counts that
字典包含各项百分比和数量统计数据
summarize how well the algorithm classified the images.
对算法的图像分类效果进行了汇总
This dictionary's key is the statistics name and the value is the statistics value.
该字典以统计数据名为键 以统计数据值为值
Model. The CNN model architecture used to classify the images.
第三个参数为 model 即用于图像分类的 CNN 模型结构
This is needed for the print statements.
输出语句少不了该参数
Print_incorrect_dogs, a boolean value that when
第四个参数是布尔值 print_incorrect_dogs
true prints incorrectly classified dogs using the results_dic dictionary.
如果该值为真 则会输出被字典 results_dic 错误分类的犬类
This parameter has the default argument of false when no misclassification are printed.
如果没有错误分类可输出 该参数就默认为  False
Print_incorrect_breed, a boolean value when true
第五个参数是布尔值 print_incorrect_breed
prints incorrectly classified dog breeds using the results_dic dictionary.
当其为真时 会输出被字典 results_dic 错误分类的犬种
This parameter has the default argument of false,
如果没有错误分类可输出
where no misclassification are printed.
参数就默认为 False
This function returns nothing because you're just printing results.
由于我们只输出结果 所以函数 print_results 没有返回内容
First this function prints out the CNN model architecture,
首先 函数会输出 CNN 模型结构
the number of images,
图像数量
the number of dog images and the number of non-dog images.
犬类图像数量和非犬类图像数量
Next it prints out all the percentages to
接着 函数会输出各项百分比
summarize how well each of the algorithms performed on image classification.
对各算法的图像分类效果进行汇总
Notice to do this iterates through
注意 为了汇总 需要对字典 results_stats 进行迭代
the results_stats dictionary looking for where the statistics started with the letter P,
为了只输出百分比
to print out only the percentages.
我们需要找出以字母 P 开头的统计数据
In this next section it prints out dog misclassification if
这个部分的函数会输出被错误分类的犬类
print incorrect dogs is true and there was a dog misclassification.
如果 print_incorrect_dogs 为真 那就意味着有犬类被错误分类了
To do this it iterates through the results_dic dictionary,
为此 函数会对字典 results_dic 进行迭代
and prints out where it finds those dog misclassification.
找出分类错误的犬类并将其输出出来
In this final section here it prints out breed misclassifications.
在最后这个部分里 函数会输出被错误分类的犬种
If print_incorrect_breed is true
print_incorrect_breed 为真
and there is a breed misclassification it iterates through
意味着有犬种被错误分类了
the results_dic dictionary to print
函数会对字典 results_dic 进行迭代
these breed misclassifications only when it finds a breed misclassification.
找到被错误分类的犬种并将其输出出来
This ends the function.
函数到此结束
The program ends with this call to run the main function.
最后 程序会调用主函数
This is the function call to the print results function within the main function.
这里 我们在主函数里调用了函数 print_results
This function returns nothing because we're just printing results.
由于我们只输出结果 所以函数没有返回内容
This function requires three but can have up to five input arguments,
函数有三个必要参数 但可以输入最多五个参数
result_dic, the dictionary with the file name as its key and a list as its value.
第一个参数是字典 result_dic 该字典以文件名为键 以列表为值
This dictionary is required argument and
是必要参数
it's needed to print the misclassified dogs and breeds.
要输出被错误分类的犬类和犬种 此函数必不可少
Results_stats_dic, the dictionary returned by the calculate_result_stats function.
第二个参数是字典 results_stats_dic 该字典由函数 calculate_result_stats 返回而出
This dictionary is required and contains all the percentages and
是必要参数 包含了各项百分比和数量统计数据
counts that summarize how well the algorithm classified the images.
对算法的图像分类效果进行了汇总
In arg.arch,
还有一个参数是 in_arg.arch
the command line argument for the CNN model architecture used to classify the images.
这是 CNN 模型结构的命令行参数 用于图像分类
This argument is required.
也是必要参数
True, a boolean value that prints
布尔值参数 True
incorrectly classified dogs using the results_dic dictionary.
此参数会输出被字典 results_dic 错误分类的犬类
This argument is not required and defaults to
不是必要参数
false where no misclassification are printed.
如果没有可输出的错误分类 则默认为 False
True, a boolean value that prints
布尔值参数 True
incorrectly classified dog breeds using the results_dic dictionary.
此参数会输出被字典 results_dic 错误分类的犬种
This argument is not required and defaults to
不是必要参数
false when no misclassification are printed.
如果没有可输出的错误分类 则默认为 False
The only temporary code is a commented out call to
这是函数唯一的临时代码 这段带注释的代码
the function to check that the default arguments work correctly.
调用了外部函数 以便检查默认参数是否正确
Let's go to the terminal window.
我们来看终端窗口
In this first terminal,
第一个终端窗口
this is from the last section where we were
运行着上一节的代码
checking that the percentages and the counts were working correctly.
当时我们检查了百分比和数量统计的正确性
We want to compare this to terminal two where we've run
现在将这些数据与第二个终端窗口里的进行比较
print results but we did the run where we're testing the default arguments.
在第二个窗口里 我们运行了 print_results 但由于运行时我们还测试了默认参数
So expect that there won't be any prints of
所以按理说 第二个窗口不会输出任何被错误分类的犬种
misclassified breeds because it's the only misclassification we have,
因为犬种分类错误是唯一的错误情况
we won't see those prints in the next terminal.
所以第二个窗口不会输出相应的内容
When we look in this next terminal,
来看第二个窗口
we see where we ran the program,
可以看到 程序运行后
we don't see any prints of misclassified breeds in
没有任何有关犬种被错误分类的输出
our numbers for the percent correct dogs not dogs and breeds,
犬类和非犬类得到正确分类的百分比
match what we saw in terminal one.
与第一个终端窗口的数据一致
So this means our program is working
可见程序无误
great and so far it seems like it's working perfectly.
到目前为止 程序运行良好
Our next check is terminal three,
接着 检查第三个终端窗口
where this time we allow the prints of misclassified breeds
这次我们允许程序输出被错误分类的犬种和犬类
and dogs but since we had no misclassified dogs it only printed the misclassified breeds,
但由于没有犬类被错误分类了 所以程序只输出分类错误的犬种
which is expected and we got the same numbers.
结果如我们所料 数据也相符
So this means our program is working perfectly.
也就是说 程序无误
You should be very excited because your program is working great.
程序运行顺利 想来你应该很兴奋了
And finally, we can run it on all three model architectures.
最后 我们可以分别用三种模型结构来运行这个程序
So in terminal four we did that with batch processing.
所以 在第四个终端窗口中 我们进行了批处理
I go over and click on the files to actually look at those results.
我来快速点击一下相关文件 让你们看看结果
That's alexnet. Here's resnet.
这是 alexnet 模型的结果 这是 resnet 的
And here's vgg. And you can compare these results to the results in the next section.
这是 vgg 的 你可以把这些数据和下一节的结果进行对比
Congratulations you've finished the lab and it looks great.
恭喜你顺利完成了 lab 任务